[{"answer": "We're learning, actually, a little bit more.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "What do we actually know about what happened here?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Very specific targets.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Do we think he had a very specific set of targets or was he stopped from being more indiscriminate?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "This is a very interesting point.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "And did they have any armed security at the school?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, you know, just like you, Piers, I often think about what happened to Gabby.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "What did you think when you heard another school shooting today?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "You know, I was optimistic that after today's meeting in the White House that there would be, you know, some statement that they could find some common ground.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "You certainly would want to encourage people who are qualified to carry a concealed firearm to be able to do so in a school zone.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "So your solution if you were there in that meeting would be to arm every school, every church, every hospital, everywhere that members of the public could be?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Also, I mean, if you go back to what happened to Gabby on that day, there was somebody legally armed, a 24-year-old man, and he didn't actually in the end tackle Jared Loughner.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "You know, how many -- I mean, where does it -- where does it end?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Well, there was a man in a Walgreens next to the Safeway that came out when he heard the shooting, pulled out his firearm, and nearly shot the man who was involved in taking down the gunman.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "I mean, is that helpful in that situation?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Well, certainly, there are a lot of options.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "What do you think of people in that position?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'd like to be able to sit down with the NRA at some point and talk to them about this.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "What is your message to the NRA?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "You know, honestly, Piers, you've kind of been a bully on this issue because what you do, and I've seen it repeatedly on your show, I watch your show, and I have seen it repeatedly.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "So why am I off the rails, Mr. Shapiro?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I have seen you do it repeatedly, Piers.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "How dare you?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "I mean, you can keep saying that, but you've done it repeatedly.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Like I say, how dare you?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Let me ask you --", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "So you only care about the kids who were being killed in Chicago as much as the kids in Sandy Hook?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "We'll come to that.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "And why don't you care about -- about banning the handguns in Chicago?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "It was -- it was an assault rifle, sure.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "What was the weapon used in Aurora in the movie theater?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I believe it's an assault weapon, correct.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What was the weapon used in the Oregon shopping mall?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "It was an assault rifle.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "What was the weapon used in Sandy Hook?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we can talk about Britain in a second.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Why is it here?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "I fear the possibility of a tyranny rising in this country in the next 50 to 100 years.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Which tyranny are you fearing yourself?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "And that's not my position.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Is that your position?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "My position is that we have to calibrate laws that are designed to get hand -- guns out of the hands of bad people and keep guns in the hands of good people who want to buy them.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "What is your position?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "I think one of the ways that you do that is by better screening for mental illness.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "How do you do that?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "I don't know whether she's a good person or a bad person.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Was Adam Lanza's mother a good person?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "No, but there is --", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Has there been any evidence to suggest she was not a good person?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Well, no, it's not a matter of -- it's not a matter of morally versus immorally --", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "ORGAN: Then she becomes a bad person, does she?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "You're right, Piers.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "So is she good or bad?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "So she goes from good to bad?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "I don't know whether you could make them less accessible to criminals.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Do you believe that if you had an assault weapon ban, statistics prove that you could dry out the supply of these guns and make them less accessible to criminals?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Because I believe and respect an Americans' rights under the Second Amendment Constitution that you kindly brought in to defend themselves with a handgun or a pistol.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Why just stop yourself at assault rifles?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Explain to me this: I can't buy this.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "If he hadn't had the assault rifle, he wouldn't have used them?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Well, we can talk drug laws another time.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Do you think that's right?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "No, I think what would make sense is laws that are calibrated to solve the problem.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Does that make sense to you?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "I think the ones that have largely been removed from the market.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Which guns would you remove?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "No, because semiautomatic just means that when you pull the trigger once, one bullet comes out.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "You wouldn't remove any semiautomatics at all?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Do you understand how an AR-15 performs when it's been modified and has a magazine?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "No, not every American.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Would you want every American to have an AR-15?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "I would stop anyone with a criminal background.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Who would you stop?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "For everybody.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "For everybody?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "If it's not public.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "So there should be a database, a national registry?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "What is astonishing to me is the left's attack on the NRA.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "When the NRA came out today, after the meeting in the White House, and just said we're not prepared to entertain any kind of new gun restrictions, what did you think about that?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "If everyone in the movie theater had been armed, everyone in the school had been armed, it wouldn't have happened.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "They instill fear?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know why Ronald Reagan wanted these --", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Why did Ronald Reagan want these assault weapons removed?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I like Reagan.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "You like Reagan, right?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "If -- I'll believe what you are saying, sure.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Did you agree with him on assault weapons?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Let me read the letter.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Why don't you tell me?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "I have been debating this for a very long time.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Do you really?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "They need them for the prospective possibility of resistance to tyranny, which is not a concern today.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Why do they need those weapons?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "It could come from the United States, because governments have gone tyrannical before, Piers.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Where do you expect the tyranny to come from?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Here's where you go into the absurd and the bullying.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Do you understand how absurd you sound?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "What's astonishing about it is that for weeks now, you have been saying that anybody who disagrees with your position is absurd, idiotic, and doesn't care about the kids in Sandy Hook.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "What is astonishing?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "The point of a civilian having an AR-15 assault weapon -- many of them are ex-military.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Let me ask you again, what is the point of a civilian having an AR-15?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "To protect against the possibility of eventual government tyranny.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "An average civilian without a criminal record, why do they need one?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "They may not turn on me.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Is that what you think?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "The reason we cannot remove AR-15 assault weapons is because the threat of your own government turning on you in a tyrannical way?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "It is because there are countervailing rights and responsibilities.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "That is your position?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Or the semiautomatic.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "What would you need a fully automatic weapon for?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Hang in there.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "What advice can you give them?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "I would love to go up to Sandy Hook.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Have you thought about going up to Sandy Hook?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Almost all the recent massacres have been young males.", "docId": "130110pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "How many young females have done this?", "qSentId": 744}]